ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York City, Dept. of Commerce and Public Events, 1961-1965 (Box 329, Folder 3)
  Invitations to attend special City functions.
- New York City, Mayor's Committee on Exploitation of Workers, 1958-1960 (Box 329, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Richard T. Levy (Secretary) on status of Union members.
- Newspapers. Corres. re Union and labor articles, 1954 (Box 329, Folder 5a-5b)
  March 1954. D.D. testimony in Harry Karsh vs Pulitzer Publishing Co. case
- National and International Labor Unions, 1932-1966 (Box 329, Folder 6)
  Arranged. 1. Unions, Gen'l. Corres. 2. Miscellaneous Unions. 3. Overlapping Unions. Correspondence bet. D.D. & officers of Union on collective agreements, strikes, merger of unions. Union contributions to strike funds, jurisdictional disputes, AFL, CIO controversy & labor related matters.
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, (A.C.W.A.), 1952-1966 (Box 329, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. Jacob Potofsky, Union report on labor record of Judge Van Voorhis, 1954
- A.C.W.A., 1939-1952 (Box 329, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of N.A. (Meat Cutters)., 1943-1965 (Box 329, Folder 8a-8b)
  I.c.w. Thomas J. Lloyd, 1958- 65; Earl Jimerson, 1946-57; Patrick J. Gorman, 1943-65.
- Meat Cutters, Hearings, 1956-1959 (Box 329, Folder 9)
  Corres. w. Norman Zukowsky (President), Int'l. Leather Goods, Plastics & Novelty Workers' Union on jurisdictional disputes bet. the two unions.
- Meat Cutters, Merger, 1954-1957 (Box 330, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. on merger of the Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers' Union & Meat Cutters, 1954; correspondence. w. Abe Feinglass & Patrick Gorman on Communist activities in union, 1955-57.
- American Federation of Hosiery and Allied Workers, 1933-1960 (Box 330, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Teachers, 1947-1966 (Box 330, Folder 3a-3c)
  I.c.w. Charles Cogen.
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l. Union, 1958-1965 (Box 330, Folder 4)
- Building Service Employees Int'l. Union, 1936-1960 (Box 330, Folder 5)
- Communications Workers of America, 1945-1965 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  Incl. correspondence. on striking telephone workers in NYC, 1947.
- Int'l. Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1930-1956 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  Corres. & printed material from Machinists on disaffiliation from AFL, 1940-46.
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1945-1965 (Box 330, Folder 8)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, 1962-1963 (Box 331, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, 1934-1961 (Box 331, Folder 2a-2c)
  Corres. w. Wm. Green & Daniel Tobin on claim by Teamsters over truckers affiliated w. Union, 1934-49.
- Int'l. Fur Workers Union (Fur Workers), 1950-1965 (Box 331, Folder 3)
- Fur Workers, 1937-1949 (Box 331, Folder 4a-4b)
  Charges by Fur Workers that Sam Herbst is organizing for CIO in Winnipeg, Canada, 1943- 44.
- Int'l. Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union, 1937-1966 (Box 331, Folder 5a-5c)
  (Formerly Int'l. Handbag, Luggage, Belt & Novelty Workers' Union) Corres. & reports from Philip Lubliner (Manager), Pocketbook Workers, Local 1, Norman Zukowsky, Ossip Walinsky on inter-union activities.
- Int'l. Longshoremen's Assoc., 1939-1964 (Box 332, Folder 1a-1d)
  Corres. & reports on expulsion of Longshoremen from AFL, 1953; reaffiliation, 1959.
- Longshoremen, Newspaper Clippings on Racketeering, 1952-1953 (Box 332, Folder 2)
- Int'l. Typographical Union, 1934-1965 (Box 332, Folder 3)
- Int'l. Union of Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1956 (Box 332, Folder 4)
- Int'l. Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (I.U.E.), 1937-1965 (Box 332, Folder 5)
- I.U.E., 1954-1959 (Box 332, Folder 6a-6b)
  Incl. correspondence. bet. D.D. (Chairman), AFL-CIO Sub-committee & George Meany on jurisdictional dispute bet. I.U.E. & Sheet Metal Workers Int'l. Assoc. at Belock Instrument Corp., 1957-59; strike at Westinghouse Corp., 1956
- Int'l. Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (U.A.W.), AFL-CIO, 1945-1966 (Box 333, Folder 1a-1c)
  I.c.w. Walter P. Reuther on Citizens Crusade Against Poverty.
- Int'l. Union, United Automobile Workers of America (AFL), 1938-1949 (Box 333, Folder 1d)
  I.c.w. Homer Martin, Lester Washburn, George Meany, William Green on internal UAW situation, loans and reaffiliation to AFL.
- U.A.W., CIO, 1942-1956 (Box 333, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. Walter P. Reuther & U.A.W. officers on internal situation, strike activities; Richard Schanck case, 1944-48.
- Nat'l. Agricultural Workers' Union, 1940-1958 (Box 333, Folder 3a-3c)
  (Formerly Nat'l. Farm Labor (Union) Corres. w. H.L. Mitchell on organizational drives, requests for funds for organizational drives & strikes.
- Nat'l. Maritime Union of America, 1937-1964 (Box 333, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. Joseph Curran.
- American Newspaper Guild (Newspaper Guild), 1937-1952 (Box 334, Folder 1a-1b)
- Office and Professional Employees Int'l. Union, 1940-1949 (Box 334, Folder 2)
- Pocketbook Workers' Union. (Affiliated w. Int'l. Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers' Union), 1939-1954 (Box 334, Folder 3a-3c)
  Hearings; I.c.w. Ossip Walinsky, reports, resolutions, financial statements, printed material by AFL Special Comm. on internal conflict.
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1937-1959 (Box 334, Folder 4)
- Seafarers Int'l. Union of N.A., 1940-1965 (Box 334, Folder 5a)
- Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, 1936-1958 (Box 334, Folder 5a-5c)
  I.c.w. Nat'l. Sharecroppers Fund, Inc., Norman Thomas, H.L. Mitchell.
- Textile Workers Union of America, 1937-1962 (Box 335, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. w. Wm. Pollack; proposed merger agreement bet. Textile Workers Union & United Textile Worker, 1958; agreement bet. Union & Textile Workers re Knitted Outerwear & Knitted Underwear Industry, Dec. 1937.
- United Garment Workers of America, 1940-1956 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Joseph McCurdy.
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers Int'l. Union, 1962-1965 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Alex Rose.
- Hatters, 1953-1959 (Box 335, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. on contributions by Union for strike relief to Hatters in strike against Hat Corp. of America; correspondence. w. Max Zaritsky prior to 1950.
- United Mine Workers of America, 1962-1966 (Box 335, Folder 5)
- Mine Workers, 1942-1957 (Box 335, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. John L. Lewis.
- United Steelworkers of America, 1937-1965 (Box 335, Folder 7a-7b)
- United Textile Workers of America, 1949-1964 (Box 335, Folder 8)
- Textile, 1942-1948 (Box 336, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. correspondence. re jurisdictional dispute bet. Textile & Union, agreement, list of shops transferred to Union.
- Upholsterers Int'l. Union of N.A., 1942-1965 (Box 336, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Sal B. Hoffman on Union loan; CIO raids.
- Misc. Unions, A., 1958 (Box 336, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. Amalgamated Lithographers of America, resolution to withdraw from AFL-CIO, Aug. 1958.
- Misc. Unions, B., 1939-1965 (Box 336, Folder 4a-4b)
  I.c.w. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1939-43; A. Philip Randolph, Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1940-65.
- Misc. Unions, C. (Box 336, Folder 5)
- Misc. Unions, D-F. (Box 337, Folder 1a-1b)
- Misc. Unions, G-H., 1934-1965 (Box 337, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Hotel & Restaurant Employees' & Bartenders' Int'l. Union on organizational drive.
- Misc. Unions, I. (Box 337, Folder 3a-3e)
- Misc. Unions, J-L. (Box 337, Folder 4)
- Misc. Unions, M-N. (Box 338, Folder 1a-1b)
- Misc. Unions, O-P. (Box 338, Folder 2)
- Misc. Unions, O., 1945-1965 (Box 338, Folder 3a-3b)
  Office Employees Int'l. Union, Local 153; correspondence. re negotiations & collective agreement w. Union.
- Misc. Unions, Q-R. (Box 338, Folder 4a-4b)
- Misc. Unions, M-S. (Box 338, Folder 5a-5b)
- Misc. Unions, T., 1966 (Box 338, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Transport Workers Union re N.Y. Transit Strike.
- Misc. Unions, U. (Box 339, Folder 1a-1d)
- Misc. Unions, V-Z. (Box 339, Folder 2)
- Overlapping Unions. American Federation of Hosiery Workers and Union, 1944 (Box 339, Folder 3)
- Overlapping Unions. American Federation of Rubber Workers and Local 92, Union, 1960 (Box 339, Folder 4)
- Overlapping Unions. Congress of Industrial Organization and American Federation of Labor, 1955-1956 (Box 339, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. George Meany, Wm. F. Schnitzler, releases, reports, statements issued jointly by AFL-CIO Unity Committee; newspaper clippings on merger of AFL, CIO into a single federation. Incl. publications by AFL-CIO Unity Committee, AFL-CIO & Union.
- Overlapping Unions. CIO and AFL., 1943-1956 (Box 339, Folder 6a-6b)
  Corres. bet. D.D., Wm. Green, Daniel Tobin, Philip Murray on establishing committee, 1947-56; correspondence., newspaper clippings, publications on ending labor feud, 1944-46; D.D. address on American labor, the war and AFL-CIO controversy, Jan. 1943.
- Overlapping Unions. CIO and AFL., 1934-1956 (Box 340, Folder 1a-1c)
  Corres. w. John Brophy, letters from John L. Lewis, Sidney Hillman, Union publications; position of Union in CIO-AFL conflict, 1934-38; From Division to Unity AFL-CIO, 1956.
- Overlapping Unions. CIO Invasion of Union, 1940-1942 (Box 340, Folder 2)
- Overlapping Unions. Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers' Int'l. Union of America & Union, 1953-1954 (Box 340, Folder 3)
- Overlapping Unions. Hoffman Mfg. Co. and Local 132, 1945 (Box 340, Folder 4)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists, and Local 132., 1944-1953 (Box 340, Folder 5)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and Local 132, 1953 (Box 340, Folder 6)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers & Locals 98, 142, 155, 1951-1953 (Box 340, Folder 7)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America & Locals 32, 102, 132, 222, 1951- 1960 (Box 340, Folder 8)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Jewelry Workers' Union and Local 66. (Box 340, Folder 9)
- Overlapping Unions. Union and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1938-1958 (Box 341, Folder 1a-1d)
- Overlapping Unions. Local 91, Union and A.C.W.A., 1939-1942 (Box 341, Folder 2a-2b)
  Bathrobes Industry, correspondence. w. Harry Greenberg, copies of letters bet. Greenberg & Sidney Hillman, releases by Union & A.C.W.A. on jurisdictional dispute in industry.
- Overlapping Unions. Union and A.C.W.A. Cloak Industry, 1940-1947 (Box 341, Folder 3a-3d)
  I.c.w. Adolph Held re dispute bet. Local 169 of A.C.W.A. & Local 105, Union, 1940-41; Emil Schlesinger brief in Bond Clothing Store case, 1947.
- Overlapping Unions. Union and A.C.W.A., 1936-1941 (Box 342, Folder 1a-1b)
  Cloak Out-of-Town, arranged alphabetically by city.
- Overlapping Unions. Union and A.C.W.A., Miscellaneous Locals, 1937-1963 (Box 342, Folder 2a-2c)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Longshoremen's Association and Local 102, 1962 (Box 342, Folder 3)
- Overlapping Unions. Int'l. Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties and Allied Products of the U.S. & Canada & Locals 98, 105, 132, 1953- 1960 (Box 342, Folder 4)
- Overlapping Unions. Pocketbook Workers Union (affiliated w. United Handbag, Leather Goods Novelty Workers) and Locals 98, 132, 155, 1946-1951 (Box 342, Folder 5)
- Overlapping Unions. Retail Clerks Int'l. Assoc. and Locals 98, 155 & 276, 1953-1960 (Box 343, Folder 1)
- Overlapping Unions. Textile Workers Union of America and Union, 1940-1963 (Box 343, Folder 2a-2b)
- Overlapping Unions. United Furniture Workers of America and Union, 1953 (Box 343, Folder 3)
- Overlapping Unions. United Garment Workers of America and Union, 1962-1964 (Box 343, Folder 4a-4d)
  Corres. w. Union officers, U.G.W., George Meany, David Cole re jurisdictional dispute over Brewton Fashions, subsidiary of Judy Bond, Inc., agreement bet. Blouse Mfrs. & Locals 10 & 25, 1962.
- Overlapping Unions. United Garment Workers and Central States Region, 1964 (Box 343, Folder 5)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Mid-West Region of Union, 1941-1943 (Box 343, Folder 6)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Pacific Coast Region, 1942-1965 (Box 343, Folder 7)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and South Jersey Region, 1941 (Box 343, Folder 8)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Southwest Region, 1947-1956 (Box 343, Folder 9)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Southwest Region, 1955-1959 (Box 344, Folder 1a-1c)
  Angelica Uniform Corp., correspondence. w. Meyer Perlstein & George Meany.
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Upper South Dept., 1945-1952 (Box 344, Folder 2)
- Overlapping Unions. U.G.W. and Winnipeg Area., 1941-1945 (Box 344, Folder 3)
- Overlapping Unions. United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers Int'l. Union, & Local 132., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 4)
- Overlapping Unions. United Mine Workers of America and Union., 1944-1950 (Box 344, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Meyer Perlstein on dispute w. Mine Workers, District 50.
- Overlapping Unions. United Retail, Wholesale and Dept. Store Employees of America., 1939-1946 (Box 344, Folder 6)
- Overlapping Unions. United Textile Workers of America and Northeast Dept., 1933-1959 (Box 344, Folder 7a-7c)
- Overlapping Unions. Upholsterers Int'l. Union of N.A. and Southwest Region, 1954-1955 (Box 344, Folder 8)
- P, 1962-1966 (Box 345, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. ltrs. from James Lipsig & AFL-CIO re purchasing or shares in Portland Reporter Publishing Co., 1962-63.
- P, 1951-1961 (Box 345, Folder 2a-2c)
- Pins and Needles, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 3)
- Plettl, Martin, 1944-1963 (Box 345, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. Labor reports.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1a-1b)
  Invitations to attend Union reception, Jan. 1961.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1c)
  Acknowledgments for D.D. support & endorsement.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1d)
  Corres. on radio programs, Garment Center Rally, campaign issues in Justice.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1e)
  Activities of Union Campaign Committee, John F. Kennedy speech at Garment Center Rally Oct. 27, 1960, excerpts from Lyndon B. Johnson speech at Liberal Party Trade Union Council meeting, Oct. 5th.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1g-1h)
  Financial matters.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1i)
  Releases, Union & non-Union.
- Politics. Campaign, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 1j)
  Misc. Itrs.
- Politics. Campaign, 1958 (Box 347, Folder 1a-1c)
  I.c.w. Ben Davidson (Exec. Dir.), Liberal Party; Independent Citizens Committee (for Harriman, DeLuca, & Hogan ticket).
- Politics. Campaign, 1957 (Box 347, Folder 2)
- Politics. Campaign, 1956 (Box 347, Folder 3a-3d)
  Incl. letter from Eleanor Roosevelt to Harlem meeting of United Labor Committee, Oct. 27th; acknowledgments from candidates for D.D. support; correspondence. on Stevenson-Kefauver presidential ticket, radio broadcasts & Garment Center Rally.
- Politics. Campaign, 1954 (Box 348, Folder 1a-1d)
  Incl. acknowledgments, correspondence. on Union contributions in campaign.
- Politics. Campaign, 1953 (Box 348, Folder 2a-2d)
  Corres. on Union & Liberal Party activities in campaign.
- Politics. Campaign, 1952 (Box 349, Folder 1a-1d)
  Corres. on Presidential election.
- Politics. Campaign, 1952 (Box 349, Folder 1e-1g)
  Union activities in states.
- Politics. Campaign, 1952 (Box 349, Folder 1g-1h)
- Politics. Campaign, 1952 (Box 349, Folder 1i)
  Radio broadcasts.
- Presidents. Union. Biographical sketches. (Box 350, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico, 1962-1966 (Box 350, Folder 2a-2f)
  Corres. w. Louis Stulberg, Clifford Depin, Jerry Schoen, Alberto Sanchez on organizational activities, negotiations w. firms.
- Puerto Rico, 1956-1958 (Box 350, Folder 3a-3c)
  Oct. 1956-58. I.c.w. Robert Gladnick on negotiations.
- Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 351, Folder 1a-1c)
  Jan-Sept. 1956. I.c.w. Robert Gladnick on negotiations.
- Puerto Rico, 1955 (Box 351, Folder 2a-2c)
- Puerto Rico. Dress Accessories Corp., 1955 (Box 351, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico. International Basic Economy Corp. (Housing Corp.), 1958 (Box 351, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. Robert Gladnick on housing projects in San Juan.
- Puerto Rico. Special Industry Committees, 1953-1960 (Box 351, Folder 5a-5c)
  (D.D., labor member of Committee #15.) Letters & reports from Lazare Teper on hearings in P.R. Corres. w. Union officers, George Meany & Labor Dept. on minimum wage hearings.
- Q, 1962-1963 (Box 352, Folder 1)
- Q, 1938-1961 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  Incl. letters from J.W. de R.-Quistgaard on D.D. portrait, 1950-52.
- R, 1962-1966 (Box 352, Folder 3a-3c)
  I.c.w. Gustave Rosenberg (Chairman), Board of Education; David Rockefeller (President), Chase Manhattan Bank re investments.
- R, 1947-1961 (Box 352, Folder 4a-4e)
  I.c.w. Lindsay Rogers (Prof.), Columbia Univ., on University matters, 1957-60; Victor Riesel on newspaper articles, 1947-53; Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr., on politics, 1949-53.
- Rand School, 1941-1955 (Box 353, Folder 1)
- Refugees. Agencies. (Box 353, Folder 2a-2e)
  Letters from agencies requesting funds & Union participation in programs for displaced persons during and after World War II; Arab refugees after 1948 Arab-Israeli conflict; arranged alphabetically by agency.
- Refugees. Agencies. Citizens Committee on Displaced Persons, 1946-1950 (Box 353, Folder 3a-3b)
- Refugees. Cases, A-C., 1940-1944 (Box 353, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. w. agencies requesting D.D.'s help in individual cases. Incl. correspondence. re Francisco Largo Caballero (President), Spanish Republic, on his incarceration in Nazi concentration camp.
- Refugees. Cases, D-G. (Box 354, Folder 1a-1b)
- Refugees. Cases, H-L., 1938-1939 (Box 354, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. correspondence. re case of Karl Kautsky.
- Refugees. Cases, M-R. (Box 354, Folder 3a-3b)
- Refugees. Cases, S-Z., 1941 (Box 354, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. w. Eleanor Roosevelt on admitting Mrs. Trotsky to U.S..
- Central States Region (C.S.), 1962-1966 (Box 355, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. letters from Frederick Siems.
- Central States, 1958-1961 (Box 355, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. report on Mobile Unit, Nov. 1958.
- C.S., Bernard Altmann Texas Corp., 1957-1961 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  Corres. re agreements, copy of agreement, 1957.
- Cloak Out-of-Town Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 355, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. George Rubin & Henoch Mendelsund.
- Cloak Out-of-Town Dept., 1940-1961 (Box 355, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. Morris P. Glushien re Manchester Modes, Inc., 1953, 1955; also correspondence. w. officers of C.O.T. re reorganization of dept., 1941
- Eastern Region (Dress and Misc.), 1940-1966 (Box 355, Folder 6a-6c)
  I.c.w. Edward Kramer,
- E.R. Majestic Specialties, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 356, Folder 1)
  Incl. correspondence., memorandum of agreement, & agreement.
- Mid-West Region, 1959-1966 (Box 356, Folder 2)
- Mid-West Region, 1933-1958 (Box 356, Folder 3a-3e)
  Corres. on organizing activities, strikes, settlements, broadsides issued by Union on organizing workers, also correspondence. re internal Union problems.
- Mid-West. Genesco, 1965-1966 (Box 356, Folder 4)
- Mid-West. H. A. Satin (Chicago, Evansville)., 1952-1956 (Box 356, Folder 5)
- Mid-West. Hole proof Hosiery Co., 1954 (Box 356, Folder 6)
- Mid-West. R and H Kaufman. (Box 356, Folder 7)
- Multi-Plant Firms., 1953 (Box 356, Folder 8)
  D.D. statement to affiliates on problems of multi-plant firms; GEB decision re policy.
- N.Y. Misc. Judy Bond, Local 25, 1961-1965 (Box 357, Folder 1a-1c)
  Corres. w. officers re Judy Bond strike in Brewton, Ala.; NLRB complaint filed by Union against Judy Bond.
- N.Y. Misc. Future Fashions, Inc., 1965 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  Incl. jurisdictional dispute bet. Dress & Waistmakers' Union, Jt. Bd. & Blouse Skirt & Sportswear Workers' Union (23-25).
- N.Y. Misc. Jerry Gilden Specialties, Inc., and Local 25, 1954-1958 (Box 357, Folder 3)
- N.Y. Misc. Puritan Fashions, 1965 (Box 357, Folder 4)
- N.Y. Misc. Russ Togs, Inc., 1965 (Box 357, Folder 5)
- N.Y. Misc. Susie Brooks, 1964 (Box 357, Folder 6)
- Northeast Dept. (formerly Cotton Dress and Misc. Trades Dept.)., 1962-1966 (Box 357, Folder 7a-7d)
  I.c.w. David Gingold, Sol C. Chaikin; correspondence. w. Allen Ebert (Business Agent) re his dismissal as officer of Union.
- Northeast Dept., 1959-1961 (Box 357, Folder 8a-8b)
- Northeast Dept., 1946-1959 (Box 358, Folder 1a-1d)
  Incl. petitions from Union members for strike benefits, 1959
- Northeast Dept. Cotton City Frocks, See S.E. Dept. (Box 358, Folder 2)
- Northeast Dept. Leslie Fay, Inc. (Wilkes-Barre, Pa., Montreal), 1955-1966 (Box 358, Folder 3)
- N.E. Dept. Picture Frocks (Dumont, N.J., Fall River, Mass., New Bedford, Mass.), 1955 (Box 358, Folder 4)
- N.E. Dept., Witlin and Shapiro (Bern-Al-Lin)., 1950-1952 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  Incl. correspondence. bet. Charles Zimmerman & Jacob Potofsky (President), A.C.W.A. re jurisdictional dispute.
- N.E. Dept. Wyoming Valley District, 1962-1964 (Box 358, Folder 6a-6c)
  Incl. petitions not to transfer Min Matheson (District Manager), Wyoming Valley District, to Director of Union Label Dept., 1963. Also correspondence. w. Min Matheson.
- N.E. Dept. Wyoming Valley District (Min L. Matheson, Mgr.), 1953-1961 (Box 358, Folder 7a-7b)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1962-1966 (Box 359, Folder 1a-1d)
  I.c.w. Nicholas Kirtzman, Sam Janis; requests from employees of Bobbie Brooks to return Eddie Milano to Ohio, 1964.
- O.-K. Region. N. Kirtzman (Director), 1957-1959 (Box 359, Folder 2a-2d)
- O.-K. Region. N. Kirtzman (Director). (Box 360, Folder 1a-1d)
- O.-K. Region. Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 360, Folder 2a-2c)
  Corres. on negotiation of agreements; audit of firm & subsidiaries.
- O.-K. Region. Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 360, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. correspondence. on negotiations of Hialeah Knitting Mills (subsidiary), Welfare Fund audit of Bobbie Brooks.
- O.-K. Region. Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 361, Folder 1a-1c)
- O.-K. Region. Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 361, Folder 2a-2b)
  Corres. renegotiations for agreements; Incl. agreements.
- O.-K. Region. B.V.D., (Piqua, Ohio; Pascagoula, Miss.), 1952-1964 (Box 361, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. N. Kirtzman, re organizational activities at B.V.D. w. Morris Glushien.
- O.-K. Region. Fashion Frocks (Cincinnati, O., Greenville, Tenn.), 1951-1960 (Box 361, Folder 4)
- O.-K. Region. G.H. Hess, Inc., 1954 (Box 361, Folder 5)
  (Louisville, O., Wheeling, W.Va.)
- O.-K. Region. Keller-Kohn. See Upper South Dept. (Box 361, Folder 5a)
- O.-K. Region. Louis Levine and Sons Dress Co., 1953-1960 (Box 361, Folder 6)
  (Cincinnati, O., Dothan, Ala.) Re negotiations.
- O.-K. Region. Perfection Garment Co. See Upper South Dept. (Box 361, Folder 6a)
- O.-K. Region. Portrait Frocks. See Southeast Dept. (Box 361, Folder 6b)
- O.-K. Region. Printz-Biederman Co., 1952-1959 (Box 361, Folder 7a-7b)
  Corres. w. Union officers on Local 200, Cleveland, O. & Local 400, Bardstown, Ky. Correspondents incl. N. Kirtzman, Meyer Perlstein, D. Solomon (Mgr.), Local 400, & Albert Buckeye (Mgr.), Local 200.
- O.-K. Region. Pitmor Sportswear, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 7c)
  See Southwest Region.
- O.-K. Region. Sue Brett, Inc., 1965 (Box 361, Folder 8)
- O.-K. Region. Western Garment Co. See Southwest Dept. (Box 361, Folder 8a)
- O.-K. Region. Wilrose Cottons, 1954 (Box 361, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Area (P. A.). Carlton Plastics, Inc., 1963 (Box 362, Folder 1)
- P.A. Mitzi Dress, 1955 (Box 362, Folder 2)
  (Miami Beach, Puerto Rico).
- Puerto Rico, Harwood Mfg. Corp., 1957-1964 (Box 362, Folder 3)
  (P.R., Upper South) Incl. letters from Jerry Schoen, Robert Gladnick (Mgr.), Local 600, on negotiation of agreements w. firm.
- Southeastern Region, 1965-1966 (Box 362, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. w. Martin Morand (Director) on organizational activities; & negotiations w. firms.
- Southeastern Region, 1965 (Box 362, Folder 4c)
  Corres. re James Belluso (Bus. Agent), suspended from Union.
- Southeastern Region, 1963-1965 (Box 362, Folder 4d)
  E. T. Kehrer.
- Southeastern Region, 1962-1964 (Box 362, Folder 4e-4f)